



# **Aqeel Ur Rehman Chishti**

Nationality: Pakistani (+92) 3142881710 Date of birth: 20/05/1996 Gender: Male

Whatsapp Messenger: +923142881710

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ageelchishti/

• Address: Near Railway Station, Goth Ghani, P/O Khas, 63100 Bahawalpur (Pakistan)

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm currently looking for a full-time or part-time SvelteKit Frontend Developer position. I'm an experienced SvelteKit Frontend Developer having 3+ years of experience in Svelte / SvelteKit, Tailwind CSS, Typescript & Javascript ES6, Django, and WordPress & Elementor. Moreover, I have specialized 1+ years of experience in Vulnerability Assessment & Management, Penetration Testing, Reconnaissance, Open-source Intelligence, System & Application Auditing, and Red Teaming Operations.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Security Analyst | Internship Bytesuit LLC [ 07/2021 - 02/2022 ]

City: Bahawalpur Country: Pakistan

## Penetration Tester & Cyber Operations Training | Apprenticeship

National Cyber Training Program (NCTP) [ 07/2020 - 09/2021 ]

City: Bahawalpur Country: Pakistan

Conduct penetration testing on several Live VM Cloud Network Environments, Websites & Web Applications, and then Report on Findings. Including Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing.

## **SvelteKit Frontend Developer | Freelancing**

Several worldwide different employer's on Upwork & Fiverr [ 08/2019 - Current ]

City: Bahawalpur Country: Pakistan

Working experience in SvelteKit Development, Python/Django Development, Landing page, Website & Web Application Development, and Web Designing.

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

## **Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (Hons.)**

National College of Business Administration & Economics (NCBA&E) [ 15/03/2015 - 30/08/2019 ]

Address: 31-A Model Town A, Sarwar Shaheed Road, 63100 Bahawalpur (Pakistan)

https://ncbae.edu.pk/

Field(s) of study: Computer Science

Final grade: CGPA: 3.5/4.0

Thesis: Marble Crafts Ecommerce Store



#### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

#### **My Digital Skills**

## Full Stack Development (Django & SvelteKit)

Javascipt / Typesript / Python / HTML & CSS / SvelteKit / Django / Object Oriented Programming (OOP) / Django REST Framework / Python Web Automation / Web Scraping / Bootstrap 5 / Svelte Js / Tailwind CSS / Wordpress + Elementor / Javascr ipt (ES6) / Git

#### **Information Security**

Penetration Testing / Vulnerability Assessment / Linux (terminal commands, Bash/Shell) / Information
Security / Cybersecurity / WPScan / SQLMap / Open Source Intelligence (OSINT) / Penetration Test (Kali tools, Nessus, CVE) / Wireshark / Metasploit Framework / OWASP Top 10 / Burp Suite / Web Application Security Testing / Nessus / Kali Linux / Nmap

#### **HONOURS AND AWARDS**

## **Ethical Hacker Nanodegree**

Udacity [ 28/06/2021 ] <a href="https://confirm.udacity.com/TLEEUM7L">https://confirm.udacity.com/TLEEUM7L</a>

#### **Penetration Testing, Network Defense & Cyber Operations**

National Cyber Training Program (NCTP) [ 09/2021 ] https://aqeelchishti.github.io/docs/pentest-pdf.png https://aqeelchishti.github.io/docs/network\_defence-pdf.png

## **Technical Support Fundamentals**

Coursera [ 12/09/2020 ]

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/9P9ZNB3RYQQ9

#### The Bits and Bytes of Computer Networking

Coursera [ 29/09/2020 ]

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/V4XW2JFTUNAP

## **Operating Systems and You: Becoming a Power User**

Coursera [ 16/10/2020 ]

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/verify/6QP35BAMRN3P

## **Crash Course on Python**

Coursera [ 24/12/2020 ]

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/FPRTQQF3KVSM

### **Linux Command Line professional**

Codecademy Pro [ 04/09/2020 ]

https://aqeelchishti.github.io/docs/Codecademy\_bash\_scripting\_certificate-aqeel-chishti.pdf

### **Python for Security Professional**

Cybrary [ 09/01/2020 ]

https://aqeelchishti.github.io/docs/cybrary-cert-python-for-security-professionals.pdf



# Certificate of Proficiency in Information Systems Management (CPISM)

Aptech Computer Education [ 09/02/2015 ]

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Urdu

Other language(s):

**English** 

**LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B2** 

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2** 

# **HOBBIES AND INTERESTS**

# **Working on Pentesting Training Platforms**

I really like to work with Penetration Testing training platforms and learn with real-world scenarios. I have already joined platforms like Hack The Box and Try Hack Me.

# **Designing Websites and Web Automation**

During my studies, I have done several Web Design and Automation projects.

## Gaming

I also like playing First Person Shooter games.

# **Playing Badminton**

I'm also a badminton player and I took part in several tournaments on the community level in my local area.